{
  "LevelId": 9,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 78,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "ENGLISH",
      "question": "language is widely spoken and used for communication in many parts of the world"
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "CONTACT",
      "question": "get in touch with someone or establish communication"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "MISSION",
      "question": "Task with purpose"
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "SURGERY",
      "question": "the treatment or repair of injuries"
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "TEACHER",
      "question": "responsible for imparting knowledge and guiding students"
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "COLUMBA",
      "question": "bird is often considered a symbol of peace"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "DESKTOP",
      "question": "computer's primary interface, often consisting of a screen, keyboard, and mouse"
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "NUCLEAR",
      "question": "Source of immense energy"
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "KEYWORD",
      "question": "Essential search term"
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BARCODE",
      "question": "Scannable identifier"
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "SCOREBOARD",
      "question": "Game's point display"
    }
  ]
}